<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Aiea Teeth Whitening - www.wemakehawaiismile.com</title>
<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com</link>
<description>Japanese Dentist Honolulu - Modern dentistry offers a wide variety of treatment options for people seeking to enhance their smile. The options range from porcelain veneers to braces</description>
<language>en-us</language>

<item>
	    <title>Aiea Cosmetic Dentist - www.wemakehawaiismile.com</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/welcome_htm.htm</link>
		<description>Japanese Dentist Honolulu - Modern dentistry offers a wide variety of treatment options for people seeking to enhance their smile. The options range from porcelain veneers to braces</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "true">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/welcome_htm.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Children's Dentistry</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/general-childrens-dentistry.htm</link>
		<description>A good general or pediatric dentist is committed to improving and maintaining the oral health of infants, children, and adolescents. Thanks to fluoride, dental sealants, and better dental habits, 55 percent of school-age children now have no cavities.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/general-childrens-dentistry.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Periodontal Therapy</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/high-tech-periodontal-therapy.htm</link>
		<description>In some cases, surgical therapy or cosmetic solutions may be necessary to correct the damage from gum disease physically and cosmetically. A periodontist can evaluate your situation and present the best treatment options for you.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/high-tech-periodontal-therapy.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Dentures</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/general-dentures.htm</link>
		<description>Saving even a few natural teeth is better than losing them all. Natural teeth or even portions of natural teeth (roots) can help you retain bone in your jaw and can act as stable supports for bridges, overdentures or removable partial dentures.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/general-dentures.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Dental Implants</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-dental-implants.htm</link>
		<description>Dental implants offer stability because they fuse to your bone. Integration of the implants into your jaw also helps your replacement teeth feel more natural and some people also find the secure fit more comfortable than conventional substitutes.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-dental-implants.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Dental Crowns</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-dental-crowns.htm</link>
		<description>The difference between these crowns and the crowns discussed previously is their coverage of the underlying tooth - the traditional crown covers the entire tooth; onlays and 3/4 crowns cover the underlying tooth to a lesser extent.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-dental-crowns.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Diagnodent</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-diagnodent.htm</link>
		<description>Many cosmetic dental offices are proud to use Diagnodent, a laser detection system that has the ability to detect hidden decay under seemingly intact tooth structure. The Diagnodent scans the area with a laser light that is harmless. </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-diagnodent.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Endodontics</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-endodontics.htm</link>
		<description>Extensive decay, an accident, tooth fracture, or gum disease can kill teeth and cause a root canal symptom such as root canal pain or a dental abscess. However, regardless of the root canal cause, your teeth can be saved using modern therapy to do root can</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-endodontics.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Vizilite</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-vizilite.htm</link>
		<description>ViziLite is a simple, painless and non-invasive instrument that improves the doctor&#039;s ability to visualize, evaluate and monitor suspicious areas at their earliest stages. ViziLite helps the doctor see what he/she can&#039;t see with the unaided eye.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-vizilite.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Smile Makeover</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-smile-makeover.htm</link>
		<description>Until fairly recently, most people were satisfied if their teeth were straight and free of stains, chips or other obvious imperfections. But in the last few years, the combination of Hollywood glamour and advances in cosmetic dentistry has led to what...</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-smile-makeover.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Porcelain Veneers page 1</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/honolulu-porcelain-veneers-1.htm</link>
		<description>Porcelain veneers are the most recent application of the art and science of cosmetic dental bonding. For decades dentists have had available to them materials which can create a durable bond to tooth enamel.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/honolulu-porcelain-veneers-1.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Tooth Whitening Intro</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/aiea-tooth-whitening-introduction.htm</link>
		<description>There are a few tooth whitening procedures available that correct discoloration of the tooth by removing the brown and yellow staining. While each work effectively, there are advantages and disadvantages to each procedure dependent upon your objectives and commitment to the processes.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/aiea-tooth-whitening-introduction.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Cosmetic Dentistry page 1</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/aiea-cosmetic-dentistry-1.htm</link>
		<description>The dentist explains the many different techniques available in the field of cosmetic dentistry and shows you the benefits! If you have ever thought about cosmetic dentistry, this guide can be extremely helpful in understanding what is possible.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/aiea-cosmetic-dentistry-1.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Zoom Whitening</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-zoom-whitening.htm</link>
		<description>Zoom! utilizes a breakthrough dual barrel chemistry that is engineered to accelerate whitening efficacy in two unique ways. First, it utilizes a breakthrough surfactant technology for improved gel penetration. Second, it helps to control the activation of </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-zoom-whitening.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Invisalign</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-invisalign.htm</link>
		<description>To date, Align has received two industry awards for its design and production of Invisalign - the 2002 Medical Design Excellence Award and the 2001 Stereolithography Excellence Award.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-invisalign.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>