<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Aiea Dentist - www.wemakehawaiismile.com</title>
<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com</link>
<description>Japanese Dentist Honolulu - Modern dentistry offers a wide variety of treatment options for people seeking to enhance their smile. The options range from porcelain veneers to braces</description>
<language>en-us</language>

<item>
	    <title>Aiea Japanese Dentist - www.wemakehawaiismile.com</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/welcome_htm.htm</link>
		<description>Japanese Dentist Honolulu - Modern dentistry offers a wide variety of treatment options for people seeking to enhance their smile. The options range from porcelain veneers to braces</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "true">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/welcome_htm.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Vizilite</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-vizilite.htm</link>
		<description>Because early detection is the key to successful outcomes, this practice has incorporated ViziLite, an FDA-cleared medical technology for oral screening to ensure that you receive the most comprehensive oral cancer screening possible.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-vizilite.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Porcelain Veneers page 2</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/honolulu-porcelain-veneers-maintenance.htm</link>
		<description>Cosmetic dental work often involves a substantial investment, and may require special maintenance to help keep it looking its best. Cosmetic dentists with many years experience in the field, have valuable insights into keeping your dental work looking great for years to come.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/honolulu-porcelain-veneers-maintenance.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Diagnodent</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-diagnodent.htm</link>
		<description>Many cosmetic dental offices are proud to use Diagnodent, a laser detection system that has the ability to detect hidden decay under seemingly intact tooth structure. The Diagnodent scans the area with a laser light that is harmless. </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-diagnodent.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Cerec Crowns</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-cerec-crowns.htm</link>
		<description>For you, the patient, this means fewer injections, less drilling, and less time out of your hectic schedule for dental care . So, why are thousands of people world wide choosing the CEREC restorative technique for their dental needs?</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-cerec-crowns.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Tooth Whitening Intro</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/aiea-tooth-whitening-introduction.htm</link>
		<description>How white an individual tooth can become from bleaching and whitening is a common question. Some whitening procedures claim they can whiten your teeth by up to nine shades, but that is highly unlikely.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/aiea-tooth-whitening-introduction.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Tooth Whitening</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/aiea-tooth-whitening.htm</link>
		<description>Supervised bleaching procedures that are done in-office and at-home have become among the most popular treatment options. In some cases, the procedure is performed entirely in the office, using a light or heat source to speed up the bleaching process.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/sep/aiea-tooth-whitening.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Laser Teeth Whitening</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/high-tech-laser-teeth-whitening.htm</link>
		<description>With the trays method you place the gel in the trays and wear the whitening gel for about an hour a day over a period of a few weeks. A dazzling smile isn&#039;t just for celebrities any more. It&#039;s also for you, because you&#039;re worth it. </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/high-tech-laser-teeth-whitening.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Zoom Whitening</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-zoom-whitening.htm</link>
		<description>The Zoom! In-Office Whitening System is a revolutionary tooth whitening procedure. It&#039;s safe effective and fast, very fast. In just over an hour, your teeth will be dramatically whiter. Zoom! Whitening is ideal for anyone looking for immediate results.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/branded-zoom-whitening.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Endodontics</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-endodontics.htm</link>
		<description>With today&#039;s modern dental techniques, having root canals done by a dentist is no longer a scary experience. Locate a dentist who is experienced in performing root canal therapy.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-endodontics.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Children's Dentistry</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/general-childrens-dentistry.htm</link>
		<description>The dramatic drop in cavities among children with regular dental care is due to regular visits to the dentist starting at an early age, professional teeth cleaning for children, proper tooth brushing habits, fluoride, and dental sealants.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/general-childrens-dentistry.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Laser Dentistry</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/high-tech-laser-dentistry.htm</link>
		<description>Our office recently purchased a water laser and have been implementing the device for various procedures.. This versatile device performs a host of both tooth and soft tissue related procedures, often times with no need for local anesthesia.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/high-tech-laser-dentistry.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Periodontics</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/general-periodontics.htm</link>
		<description>Periodontal treatment starts with prevention: regular cleanings and good hygeine habits are excellent precautions to take to avoid gum disease.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/general-periodontics.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Aiea  - Non Metal Fillings</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-non-metal-fillings.htm</link>
		<description>With the amazing advancements that have been made in modern dentistry, metal amalgam fillings are now obsolete. Today&#039;s tooth-colored composites are safer, stronger, more attractive and more enduring alternatives to metal.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/cosmetic-non-metal-fillings.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Honolulu  - Digital Xrays</title>
		<link>http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/high-tech-digital-xrays.htm</link>
		<description>Digital X-rays are images that are taken digitally and loaded into a computer file especially for a specific patient.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.wemakehawaiismile.com/glossary/high-tech-digital-xrays.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>